

PROFILE

I'm an enthusiastic, responsible and hardworking IT person. Being worked on different projects helped me to adapt to the changes quickly and made me a mature team worker. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using my own initiative. I am able to work well under pressure and adhere to strict deadlines.

CONTACT

PHONE

+977-9861498184

QADDRESS:

Dhulikhel-7, Kavrepalanchok

EMAIL

metiwariakrosh02@gmail.com

LANGAUGES

Nepali (Advanced speaking) Hindi (Fluent speaking) English (Fluent speaking) Tamang (Fluent speaking)

HOBBIES

Sport Travel Social media Watching movies Hiking

AKROSH TIWARI

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technology NIST College [Banepa, Kavre]

2015 - 2020

[Waiting final result of my bachelor program.]

+2 Science

Guinness Int'l College [Gaushala, Kathmandu]

2013 - 2015

[58% on aggregate]

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancing on different project

March 2020 - Feb 2021

I mainly worked as a FrontEnd related work on a different projects.

Abhiyantrik Technology [Web development intern]

Dec 2019 - March 2020

I worked as a web developer building a startup product. Being a first real-world software development experience in the top IT firm of the country, I got a chance to:

- Learn the software development ecosystem and work as a team,
- Harness my technical skills through guided mentorships,
- Network with the expertise of the software industry.

PROJECTS

Abhiyantrik Website [Final year intern project]

- A complete frontend Website developing
- Tool used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Media query

Portfolio website [Intern first project]

- Personal portfolio website developing
- Tool used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Media query

Vegetable and Meat Mart [Seven semester final project]

• Developed using core PHP, Laravel and MySQL

SKILL AND ABILITIES

1.Logical and structural thinking

2. Cooding in multiple languages:

- High level programming knowledge (JAVA, C, C++)
- Web development with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP.
- Working knowledge in framework and CMS (Laravel, Bootstrap, ReactJs, WordPress,)
- Version control (Git)
- Database management system (MySQL)
- Operating system (Ubuntu Linux, WindoowsXp7&10)
- Tools used (Photoshop, XD, Visual Studio Code)